getflywheel.com 2019-07-17

# Flywheel | Privacy Policy

Fancy Chap, Inc. (“us”, “we”, or “our”) operates getflywheel.com (the “Site”).

This Privacy Policy informs you of our policies regarding the collection, use and disclosure of personally identiﬁable information we receive from users of the Site. It also describes the choices available to you regarding our use of your Personal Information (also known as “personal data”) and how you can access and update that information.  Personal Information is information about you that can be used, directly or indirectly, to identify you (e.g., name, email address, mailing address, date of birth).

We use your Personal Information only for the purposes of registration, billing, and improving the Site. By using the Site, you agree to the collection and use of Personal Information in accordance with this Privacy Policy. Unless otherwise deﬁned in this Privacy Policy, capitalized terms used herein shall have the same meanings as in our [Terms of Service](https://getflywheel.com/legal/terms-service/).

## **Information We Collect**

While using the Site, we may ask you to provide us with certain Personal Information that can be used to contact or identify you in order to use features of the Site that are only available to registered users.  We may also collect contact information so that you can place orders, request information and request support.

### **Personal Information**

To create or update an account, you supply us with an email address, phone number, password, domain and/or other similar account details.  In addition, you provide us with billing details, such as credit card information, banking information and/or billing address.

### **Inquiries**

When you contact us we may ask for information that allows us to validate the inquiry, request specific information related to the reason you have contacted us, or contact you upon resolution of your inquiry.

### **Log Data**

Like many site operators, we collect information that your browser sends whenever you visit the Site (“Log Data”). This Log Data may include information such as: your computer’s Internet Protocol (“IP”) address, browser type, browser version, the time and date of your visit, the pages of our Site that you visit, the time you spend on those pages, and other site usage statistics. We use this information to help personalize search results, diagnose problems with our services, and to administer the Site.  This is not linked to any Personal Information, except to the extent necessary to prevent fraud or abuse on our system.

### **Information Collected By Our Customers**

Our customers may collect personal data in connection with the service we provide to them. Our customers control the personal data they collect, and we will not use or disclose that personal data except as authorized or directed by the customer in the course of our provision of the services. If your personal data is controlled by one of our customers and you have concerns about the way that data is managed, please contact that customer directly.

### **Cookies**

We use cookies and similar technologies in the Site that help us collect information. The Site may also include cookies and similar tracking technologies of third parties, which may collect information about you via the Site and across other websites and online services. For more details about how we use these technologies, please see our [Cookie Policy](https://getflywheel.com/legal/cookie-policy/).

## **How We Use Information**

We strongly believe in both minimizing the Personal Information we collect and limiting its use and purpose to only that (1) for which we have been given permission, (2) as necessary to deliver the services, or (3) as we might be required or permitted for legal compliance or other lawful purposes. 

### **Communicating With You**

We will only use the Personal Information we collect as reasonably necessary (a) to allow you to use and interact with the Site; (b) to provide the services to you as our customer; (c) to inform our continued development of the Site and the services; (d) to communicate with you from time to time in response to your requests for information or as may be relevant to your account with us; (e) to send marketing communications related to the services we provide; (f) as required by applicable law or legal requirements pertaining to records retention or for internal administrative purposes; or (g) as specifically authorized by you in writing.

### **E-mail**

From time to time, we may use your Personal Information to contact you by e-mail concerning our services. These communications are often intended to inform you of important information regarding your account, or about general services provided by us and/or its affiliates. If you do not want to receive email from us or our affiliates regarding new services, please click the “unsubscribe” link which is included at the bottom of any email you receive from us. However, in order to fulfill our service obligations to you, we will continue to send you emails regarding your account administration, as well as any necessary information, such as renewal notices and instructions. By providing us with your email address you consent to receiving communications from us electronically and all notices, disclosures and other communications that we provide to you electronically satisfy any legal requirement that such communications be in writing.

### **Compliance With Legal Or Law Enforcement Requests**

We cooperate with government and law enforcement officials and private parties to enforce and comply with the law. We will disclose any information about you to government or law enforcement officials or private parties as we, in our sole discretion, believe necessary or appropriate to respond to claims and legal process (such as subpoena requests), to protect our property and rights or the property and rights of a third party, to protect the safety of the public or any person, or to prevent or stop activity we consider to be illegal or unethical.  When permitted, we will disclose to any customer that is the subject of a government investigation and any data requests pertaining to customers’ Personal Information and/or hosted data. 

### **Transfer of Personal Information Abroad**

If you utilize our services from a country other than the country where our servers are located, your communications with us may result in transferring your Personal Information across international borders.  Also, when you call us or initiate a chat, we may provide you with support from outside your country of origin. In these cases, your Personal Information is handled according to this Privacy Policy.

## **Security**

The security of your Personal Information is important to us, and we use generally accepted security measures to protect against the loss, misuse or alternation of the information under our control, but remember that no method of transmission over the Internet, or method of electronic storage, is 100% secure. We strive to use commercially acceptable means to protect your Personal Information, but we cannot guarantee its absolute security.

If you have any questions about the security of your Personal Information, you can contact us at [[email protected]](https://web.archive.org/cdn-cgi/l/email-protection#b9dad6d4c9d5d0d8d7dadcf9dedccddfd5c0ced1dcdcd597dad6d4).  We may retain your information for as long as your account is active or as needed to provide you services, comply with our legal obligations, resolve disputes and enforce our agreements.

## **EU-U.S. Privacy Shield Framework**

We are a voluntary participant in the EU-U.S. Privacy Shield Framework (“EU Framework”), which you can learn more about at the U.S. Department of Commerce’s Privacy Shield site at [https://www.privacyshield.gov](https://www.privacyshield.gov/). We are committed to the principles of the EU Framework and we subject all Personal Information we collect to those principles. As a participant, we are subject to the investigatory and enforcement powers of the U.S. Federal Trade Commission and any other authorized U.S. agency.

We may be required to disclose Personal Information in response to lawful requests by public authorities, including complying with national security or law enforcement requirements. In addition, we comply with the onward transfer liability provisions regarding your Personal Information.

You have the right to access Personal Information we have collected about you and can request us to make updates or corrections to your Personal Information. You also have the right to request that we delete your data if you believe it has been processed in violation of the EU Framework principles.

In compliance with the Privacy Shield principles, we commit to resolve complaints about our collection or use of your personal information. EU individuals with inquiries or complaints regarding our Privacy Shield policy should first contact us at [[email protected]](https://web.archive.org/cdn-cgi/l/email-protection#ddadafb4abbcbea49dbab8a9bbb1a4aab5b8b8b1f3beb2b0).

We are committed to cooperate with EU data protection authorities (“DPAs”) and to comply with the advice given by such authorities with regards to unresolved Privacy Shield complaints concerning human resources data transferred from the EU in the context of the employment relationship.

Further, we are committed to refer unresolved Privacy Shield complaints to TrustArc, an alternative dispute resolution provider located in the United States. If you do not receive timely acknowledgment of your complaint from us, or if we have not addressed your complaint to your satisfaction, please visit <https://www.trustarc.com/consumer-resources/dispute-resolution>. for more information or to file a complaint. The services of TrustArc are provided at no cost to you.

You may also, under certain conditions, invoke binding arbitration. The process for binding arbitration is described at the Privacy Shield site: <https://www.privacyshield.gov/article?id=How-to-Submit-a-Complaint>.

The list of participants in the EU Framework is available at [https://www.privacyshield.gov/list](https://www.privacyshield.gov/list). 

**Other than as described in this Privacy Policy, we will not give any information about you to others without your express permission.**

## **Swiss-U.S. Privacy Shield**

We comply with the Swiss-U.S. Privacy Shield as set forth by the U.S. Department of Commerce regarding the collection, use, and retention of Personal Information from Switzerland. We have certified that we adhere to the Swiss-U.S. Privacy Shield Principles of Notice, Choice, Accountability for Onward Transfer, Security, Data Integrity and Purpose Limitation, Access, and Recourse, Enforcement, and Liability. To learn more about the Swiss-U.S. Privacy Shield and to view our certification, visit [https://www.privacyshield.gov](https://www.privacyshield.gov/).

In compliance with the Privacy Shield principles, we commit to resolve complaints about our collection or use of your personal information. Swiss individuals with inquiries or complaints regarding our Privacy Shield policy should first contact us at [[email protected]](https://web.archive.org/cdn-cgi/l/email-protection#6313110a1502001a23040617050f1a140b06060f4d000c0e).

## **Third Party Service Providers**

We may at times provide information about you to third parties to provide various services on our behalf, such as processing credit card payments, serving advertisements, performing analyses of our services, and customer relationship management.  We will only share information about you that is necessary for the third party to provide the requested services. These companies are prohibited from retaining, sharing, storing or using your Personal Information for any secondary purposes.

## **Supplemental Information**

We may receive information about you from other sources, including publicly available databases or third parties from whom we have purchased data, and combine this data with information we already have.  If others give us your information, we will only use that information for the specific reason for which is was provided to us.

## **What Happens to My Personal Information When I Terminate My Account?**

When your account is terminated (either voluntarily or involuntarily) all of your Personal Information is deleted and/or anonymized. However, deactivation of your account does not mean your Personal Information has been deleted from our database entirely.  We may keep your Personal Information for as long as reasonably required to meet the purposes described herein. Additionally, we will retain this information as required by law, as necessary to comply with our legal obligations, resolve disputes, and enforce our agreements.

## **Your Rights Over Personal Information We Control**

Upon request we will provide you with information about whether we hold, or process on behalf of a third party, any of your Personal Information.  You may access, correct, or request deletion of your personal information by contacting us at [[email protected]](https://web.archive.org/cdn-cgi/l/email-protection#2a5a58435c4b49536a4d4f5e4c46535d424f4f4604494547). 

To deactivate your account, please contact us [https://getflywheel.com/help](https://getflywheel.com/help)

We will respond to your request for access or to modify or deactivate your information within thirty (30) days.

Note that when your Personal Information is reasonably necessary for us to provide you services, or for the operation of our network, the collection, use and disclosure of Personal Information is required and you cannot opt-out or delete the information without terminating your services.  If your Personal Information is not reasonably necessary for the provisioning of the services or for the operation of our system, you will have the choice to withdraw your consent by opting out. For example, where you have provided express consent for the use of specific services for marketing purposes, you can opt-out later on as you like.  Similarly, you can opt-out of your Personal Information being used for a variety of marketing communications by us, including telemarketing or addressed marketing mail, or commercial electronic messages like emails and SMS messages, at any time by modifying your subscription settings. 

## **Links to Other Sites**

Our Site may contain links to other sites that are not operated by us. If you click on a third-party link, you will be directed to that third party’s site. We strongly advise you to review the Privacy Policy of every site you visit. We have no control over, and assume no responsibility for, the content, privacy policies, or practices of any third-party sites or services.

## **Changes to This Privacy Policy**

Fancy Chap, Inc. may update this Privacy Policy from time to time. We will notify you of any changes by posting the new Privacy Policy on the Site. You are advised to review this Privacy Policy periodically for any changes.

## **Age Restrictions**

Our services are not targeted to, intended to be consumed by or designed to entice individuals under the age of 18. If you know of or have reason to believe anyone under the age of 18 has provided us with any Personal Information, please contact us.

## **Contact Us**

If you have any questions about this Privacy Policy or any complaints about how we use your Personal Information, please contact us.

_This Privacy Policy was last modified on[September 17, 2018](https://github.com/getflywheel/legal/commit/2de7bff103dbd7ea0ab883b778d26568192f56a2)._
